Hello I'm Mišo Subotić Patrisa Lumumbe 32 Belgrade, 11030 061/111 30 32 misosubotic90@gmail.com



#### A little bit about me

I like to call myself a multimedia artist with business oriented thinking well versed in social media. My passions are video editing and recording, photography, sound editing, gaming and glitchart. One of the things I'm most proud of is building a large Facebook community around GIF's (3.7 million) from the ground up and organically in less than 2 years.

# Work experience

May 2020 - September 2020

Niche Media DOO; Belgrade, Serbia - Head of business development

- Market research and creating new opportunities for the company
- Weekly strategy and coordination meetings with local and international teams
- Developing new products and services
- Coordinating content production and distribution for social media
- Writing proposals

February 2020 - May 2020

Niche Media DOO; Belgrade, Serbia - Video Editor and community manager

- Producing video content in line with pages branding (daily)
- Researching for new trends
- Keyword and hashtag research
- Distributing content to social media pages

June 2016 - March 2018

#### Wallgif.com/Gif Porn; Tallinn, Estonia - Founder and chief strategist

- Developing and implementing the initial Facebook growth strategy
- Visual branding
- Daily content creation (short videos, slideshows etc..)
- Communicating with the audience (comments, messages)
- Client acquisition and retention
- Remote team hiring and management (video artists, motion graphics designers, developers and community managers)
- Social media content planning calendar (monthly)
- Finding various artists for Facebook Live shows (biweekly)
- Generating reports and planning growth strategy's based on the results (monthly)
- Website management (Wordpress)
- Live customer support using Tawk.to (6-10 hours daily)

• Various marketing activities (affiliate marketing, email marketing, influencer outreach, facebook and instagram ads)

#### Apr 2015 - Oct 2016

## Alternativna Televizija ATV, Banjaluka - Broadcast designer

- Working with the various marketing department team members to deliver required assets
- Managing the workflow and direction for the graphics on each broadcast
- Provide general assistance in the newsroom
- Providing motion design and animation for projects ranging from network branding elements, on-air promos, bumpers, secondary on-air messaging, sales/marketing materials and more
- Collaborate with Sr. designer staff, vendors and freelance designers to meet the creative and production goals of the department and individual projects

### Mar 2013 - Sep 2014

# K3 TV, Prnjavor - Cameraman and montage

- Planning and developing visual representation of the story with the correspondent/reporter
- Filming and recording audiovisual material to be edited and packaged for news broadcasts
- Using the correct lighting and sound recording techniques complying with broadcast standards
- Video and audio editing of news stories filmed on location
- Performing basic maintenance of camera equipment
- Editing sequences using Adobe Premiere Pro and sending via FTP using broadband network

#### Education

2009 - Present

Banjaluka College BLC, Banjaluka - Graphics design and visual communications 2005 - 2009

Srednja građevinska škola Rada Vranješević, Prnjavor- Civil engineering

# Software, CMS and SaaS:

Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe After Effects, Ableton Live, Adobe Audition, Tawk.to, Wordpress, MS Office, Canva, Hootsuite, Google docs, sheets, slides

### **Public speaking:**

"KONVERZIJA" BANJALUKA, April 2017

"Kako su veliki brendovi iskoristili GIF-ove u svoju korist"

"WEBIZ EDU" SUBOTICA, November 2017

"Do you speak GIF"